Okay!
Yeah!
Got it!
Alright!
No!
Negative!
Nope!
What?!
I can't do that!
Huh!
Contact, north!
Contact, northeast!
Contact, east!
Contact, southeast!
Contact, south!
Contact, southwest!
Contact, west!
Contact, northwest!
Enemy down!
Dead!
Enemy dead!
Okay, down!
I clipped him!
Ah...f***! A-ah!
Dead! D...dead!
Oh, God!
I need help!
Give me backup!
Hey, I need backup!
We need smoke!
Use your smoke! Use it!
Throw the smoke, come on!
Stop! Wait! Wait!
I come with you, hold on!
I come with you!
Faster!
We need to go, come on!
Alright, get in!
Give up, now! Drop your weapon!
Just surrender! Give up!
Get down on the ground
You going to die, idiot! Why not give up?!
Ha-ha! Run!
Show yourself! We will fight!
Wut, are you p***, b****, uh?!
Why you're silent?! S*** yourselves?!
Run to mommy! Run, b****!
Run, f*****s!
Oh, you like to talk, uh?
Shut up!
Come here, f****!
F*** you!
You're wasting your breath!
Come here! Why the f*** are you hiding, uh?!
Wut, are you chicken (p***), uh?!
Come here, f***face!
Shut the f***face up, b****!
Shut up!
F*** you!
Suck a d***, m**********r!
A f*****g carp! What an annoying nerd, f***!
Get me the radio!
Observer, let's get some fire support!
Where is an Observer?!
Come on, I need an Observer
I need a f*****g radio, come on!
Where is that Observer, uh?!
Can I get the radio?
Radio?!
Observer?!
Guys, come on! Radio, for f***'s sake?!
We have fire support! Let's f*****g use it, uh?!
We should call for fire support!
Look through the binoculars! Call something in!
Come on! Let's get some mortars or something!
You want me to request fire support?!
I can order fire support! What do you want?!
Commander, I call something in?!
Observer ready!
Right here, come on!
Ready!
Commander, you want me to call something in?!